[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 1, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 DISPATCHER: Does he look hurt to you?", "question_tokens": ["UNIDENTIFIED", "911", "DISPATCHER", ":", "Does", "he", "look", "hurt", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "CD", "NNP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 2, "answer": "I can't see him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "see", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Well, unfortunately, because Florida has this absurd \"Stand Your Ground\" law which makes it very, very difficult to successfully prosecute even people who may have deliberately and willfully shot because all they have to do is raise a plausible claim of self-defense and all kinds of restrictions kick in.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "unfortunately", ",", "because", "Florida", "has", "this", "absurd", "``", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "''", "law", "which", "makes", "it", "very", ",", "very", "difficult", "to", "successfully", "prosecute", "even", "people", "who", "may", "have", "deliberately", "and", "willfully", "shot", "because", "all", "they", "have", "to", "do", "is", "raise", "a", "plausible", "claim", "of", "self-defense", "and", "all", "kinds", "of", "restrictions", "kick", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "CC", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "EX", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "When you saw the FBI today, pictures of them crawling all over the crime scene, is this good or is it too late for this case?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "the", "FBI", "today", ",", "pictures", "of", "them", "crawling", "all", "over", "the", "crime", "scene", ",", "is", "this", "good", "or", "is", "it", "too", "late", "for", "this", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, you know, I'd like to think it's never too late, they may get something just from the location and -- but there can't be anything left there now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'d", "like", "to", "think", "it", "'s", "never", "too", "late", ",", "they", "may", "get", "something", "just", "from", "the", "location", "and", "--", "but", "there", "ca", "n't", "be", "anything", "left", "there", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["FBI"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Now if that is genuine and they were inflicted by Trayvon Martin, how does that change the case you?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "if", "that", "is", "genuine", "and", "they", "were", "inflicted", "by", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "how", "does", "that", "change", "the", "case", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, you don't know still.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "know", "still", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eric Deggans"]}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "How do you know that somebody didn't want to try to make it look like they've been attacked and sort of waiting for the police and there's a dead body on the ground?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "that", "somebody", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "try", "to", "make", "it", "look", "like", "they", "'ve", "been", "attacked", "and", "sort", "of", "waiting", "for", "the", "police", "and", "there", "'s", "a", "dead", "body", "on", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Let me bring in Eric Deggans here.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "bring", "in", "Eric", "Deggans", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Is it -- is it dangerous that the media keep putting this stuff out there and basically convicting or acquitting based on every new twist and turn?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "is", "it", "dangerous", "that", "the", "media", "keep", "putting", "this", "stuff", "out", "there", "and", "basically", "convicting", "or", "acquitting", "based", "on", "every", "new", "twist", "and", "turn", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, what I think is dangerous is that people take the facts that reporters are digging up and they're making suppositions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "think", "is", "dangerous", "is", "that", "people", "take", "the", "facts", "that", "reporters", "are", "digging", "up", "and", "they", "'re", "making", "suppositions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What do you think of this from a legal point of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "this", "from", "a", "legal", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "Well, I think there's a big difference between arrest which is a formal legal proceeding for which you need probable cause under the statute.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "big", "difference", "between", "arrest", "which", "is", "a", "formal", "legal", "proceeding", "for", "which", "you", "need", "probable", "cause", "under", "the", "statute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eric"]}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Can I break in for a minute?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "break", "in", "for", "a", "minute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "I'm just going to play -- just going to play a clip here, Eric, and I'll come to you after this.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "going", "to", "play", "--", "just", "going", "to", "play", "a", "clip", "here", ",", "Eric", ",", "and", "I", "'ll", "come", "to", "you", "after", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 DISPATCHER: Do you need police, fire or medical?", "question_tokens": ["UNIDENTIFIED", "911", "DISPATCHER", ":", "Do", "you", "need", "police", ",", "fire", "or", "medical", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "CD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Maybe both.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Who was screaming there, Robert?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "was", "screaming", "there", ",", "Robert", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "That's my brother.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "my", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What did you want to say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "want", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, one thing I wanted to point out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "thing", "I", "wanted", "to", "point", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "How significant is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Well, I think the voice print comparison is really, really interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "voice", "print", "comparison", "is", "really", ",", "really", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "I mean certainly it seem on the forensic side, the local police here have been incredibly lax, haven't they?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "certainly", "it", "seem", "on", "the", "forensic", "side", ",", "the", "local", "police", "here", "have", "been", "incredibly", "lax", ",", "have", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I don't -- I hate to judge police.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "hate", "to", "judge", "police", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "That it seems to have been just as skewed on the night against a young black teenage boy?", "question_tokens": ["That", "it", "seems", "to", "have", "been", "just", "as", "skewed", "on", "the", "night", "against", "a", "young", "black", "teenage", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, that's the question that is bothering everyone.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "question", "that", "is", "bothering", "everyone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Alan, your last word?", "question_tokens": ["Alan", ",", "your", "last", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, I think there's a big difference between facts and admissible facts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "big", "difference", "between", "facts", "and", "admissible", "facts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Senator", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "great", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ":", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Do you believe all things considered, all the information we now have, that it would be the correct thing to do for George Zimmerman to be arrested?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "all", "things", "considered", ",", "all", "the", "information", "we", "now", "have", ",", "that", "it", "would", "be", "the", "correct", "thing", "to", "do", "for", "George", "Zimmerman", "to", "be", "arrested", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "You know what, I'm not going to weigh into the -- to the particulars of this case.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "weigh", "into", "the", "--", "to", "the", "particulars", "of", "this", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", ":", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, I mean, the \"Stand Your Ground\" law is to -- is to allow people to be able to protect themselves and make sure that they have the right to self-defense.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "the", "``", "Stand", "Your", "Ground", "''", "law", "is", "to", "--", "is", "to", "allow", "people", "to", "be", "able", "to", "protect", "themselves", "and", "make", "sure", "that", "they", "have", "the", "right", "to", "self-defense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "But given the sheer number of cases now of people getting access to firearms who simply shouldn't have them, and who then go on to commit this kind of crimes, is it time for a big review of gun law in America?", "question_tokens": ["But", "given", "the", "sheer", "number", "of", "cases", "now", "of", "people", "getting", "access", "to", "firearms", "who", "simply", "should", "n't", "have", "them", ",", "and", "who", "then", "go", "on", "to", "commit", "this", "kind", "of", "crimes", ",", "is", "it", "time", "for", "a", "big", "review", "of", "gun", "law", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "No, it's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "At what point would you judge as a politically astute man that this would become damaging for you to stay in the race if it was perceived that you were damaging the chances of the party to defeat Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["At", "what", "point", "would", "you", "judge", "as", "a", "politically", "astute", "man", "that", "this", "would", "become", "damaging", "for", "you", "to", "stay", "in", "the", "race", "if", "it", "was", "perceived", "that", "you", "were", "damaging", "the", "chances", "of", "the", "party", "to", "defeat", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Yes, you know, I'm going to make the decision not based on what's good for me or not good for me.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "make", "the", "decision", "not", "based", "on", "what", "'s", "good", "for", "me", "or", "not", "good", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "How could you be happy, from that position, in telling 30 million Americans who are now hoping and expecting to be brought under health care cover in America when they couldn't have afforded it otherwise, you're not going to get it; that is going to be my position; my first act as president would be to throw that out, so you guys don't get health cover?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "you", "be", "happy", ",", "from", "that", "position", ",", "in", "telling", "30", "million", "Americans", "who", "are", "now", "hoping", "and", "expecting", "to", "be", "brought", "under", "health", "care", "cover", "in", "America", "when", "they", "could", "n't", "have", "afforded", "it", "otherwise", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "get", "it", ";", "that", "is", "going", "to", "be", "my", "position", ";", "my", "first", "act", "as", "president", "would", "be", "to", "throw", "that", "out", ",", "so", "you", "guys", "do", "n't", "get", "health", "cover", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Well, I would say to 300 million Americans that my first act as president is to liberate you from a government program that is going to dictate to you not only your economic choices when it comes to health care, but also your religious choices when it comes to health care.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "say", "to", "300", "million", "Americans", "that", "my", "first", "act", "as", "president", "is", "to", "liberate", "you", "from", "a", "government", "program", "that", "is", "going", "to", "dictate", "to", "you", "not", "only", "your", "economic", "choices", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "health", "care", ",", "but", "also", "your", "religious", "choices", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "health", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "What about people with preexisting conditions who would cease to get cover if you repealed this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "people", "with", "preexisting", "conditions", "who", "would", "cease", "to", "get", "cover", "if", "you", "repealed", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Why are people buying more cars when gas prices are so expensive?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "people", "buying", "more", "cars", "when", "gas", "prices", "are", "so", "expensive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "JJR", "NNS", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Well, I think there's a couple factors running around here.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "'s", "a", "couple", "factors", "running", "around", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Did it effectively save the industry?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "effectively", "save", "the", "industry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Well, I think when we had the situation in the industry, we -- we went down to support the hearings down in Washington.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "when", "we", "had", "the", "situation", "in", "the", "industry", ",", "we", "--", "we", "went", "down", "to", "support", "the", "hearings", "down", "in", "Washington", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "So when Mitt Romney attacks the bailout, he got it completely wrong, didn't he?", "question_tokens": ["So", "when", "Mitt", "Romney", "attacks", "the", "bailout", ",", "he", "got", "it", "completely", "wrong", ",", "did", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Well, again, everybody has different viewpoints on this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "again", ",", "everybody", "has", "different", "viewpoints", "on", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "I had Howard Schultz from Starbucks on last week, talking about a new sense of moral capitalism, where companies like Starbucks Apple and, dare I say it, Ford, rather than building big plants in Mexico, should be building plants like that in America, shouldn't you, and bringing jobs home, even if it's more expensive to do that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "had", "Howard", "Schultz", "from", "Starbucks", "on", "last", "week", ",", "talking", "about", "a", "new", "sense", "of", "moral", "capitalism", ",", "where", "companies", "like", "Starbucks", "Apple", "and", ",", "dare", "I", "say", "it", ",", "Ford", ",", "rather", "than", "building", "big", "plants", "in", "Mexico", ",", "should", "be", "building", "plants", "like", "that", "in", "America", ",", "should", "n't", "you", ",", "and", "bringing", "jobs", "home", ",", "even", "if", "it", "'s", "more", "expensive", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, we actually are bringing jobs back home.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "actually", "are", "bringing", "jobs", "back", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks", "Starbucks Apple", "Ford"], "LOCATION": ["Mexico", "America"], "PERSON": ["Howard Schultz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "How many people do you employ worldwide?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "people", "do", "you", "employ", "worldwide", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Worldwide, we probably employ somewhere in the neighborhood of 160,000.", "answer_tokens": ["Worldwide", ",", "we", "probably", "employ", "somewhere", "in", "the", "neighborhood", "of", "160,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "RB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "How many of that would be in America?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "of", "that", "would", "be", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "In the U.S. here, we employ about 22,000 or 23,000 salaried employees, and about 45,000 to 50,000 hourly employees.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "U.S.", "here", ",", "we", "employ", "about", "22,000", "or", "23,000", "salaried", "employees", ",", "and", "about", "45,000", "to", "50,000", "hourly", "employees", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "And what was that initial figure you gave me, the 160,000, are they all salaried or are they hourly and salaried?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "that", "initial", "figure", "you", "gave", "me", ",", "the", "160,000", ",", "are", "they", "all", "salaried", "or", "are", "they", "hourly", "and", "salaried", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "DT", "CD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "No, that's hourly and salaried.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "hourly", "and", "salaried", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "As a business?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]